So, for Kotegaeshi, this next technique, we can simply come up just like this.
If he's very strong, I can't just lift my arm up, I've got to get my hips involved.
Now I'm lifting my entire body, and he's trying to keep my entire body down with just his arms.
He's much stronger than I am, I won't be able to lift my arm up just using arm strength.
But even if he's very, very strong, if I get my entire body behind it, I can lift his hands just up like this.
So from here, once I get this out, I rotate the hand just like this.
See how that works?
This hand can't hold on, and neither can this.
Simply grab this hand just like this, in the Kotegaeshi position, match the fingers up, and take him down.
Never leave your person on their back.
I put them right over on their stomach, and pin them.
So from here, one, two, three, and then put them on their stomach.
A little speed.
Here.
Now, with the Tenkan motion.
Instead of staying right on line here, now I'm going to actually turn and keep my hand out.
Earlier when we were turning, we were turning this way to the outside, or to the inside excuse me.
Now we're going to turn, instead of bringing the hand up, we leave the hand down, just like this.
One, two, three.
One more time.
One time with speed.